

Maxim Sheshukov



Berlin, Germany



+4915256004078



sheshukovmaxim@gmail.com



go-maxus-go

A results-oriented software engineer with 8 years of work experience. Well-versed in producing efficient, reusable and readable code. Initiative and creative, constantly looking for ways for improvement. Some of my personal projects are Foody (Flutter), Marbles Puzzle (Qt, QML), di (C++).

Work experience

Software Engineer C++ 06/2019 - nowadays

Lead Software Engineer C++/Qt 11/2018 - 03/2019

Software Engineer C++ 01/2018 - 11/2018

Software Engineer C++/Qt 10/2017 - 12/2017

Software Engineer C++/Qt 03/2016 - 10/2017

Software Engineer C++

11/2013 - 03/2016

BinarySpaces, Berlin, Germany

- Reduced project save time by 50% by implementing data cache in RAM.
- Implemented a release MVP feature Rotary Table for machine setup.

Escape Technology, Moscow, Russia

• Implemented moving avatars like in Telegram messenger.

Luxoft, Moscow, Russia

Added a debugger for Lua scripts.

2GIS, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Implemented the algorithm for choosing the fastest server.

Movavi, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Implemented a Slideshow Maker that became a successful product.

SoftLab-NSK, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Designed a no bullets biathlon training system for children.

Education

Computer science / Physics master's degree 09/2006 - 06/2012

Novosibirsk State University, Novosibirsk, Russia

• Section of automation of physical and technical research. Department of physics.

Skills

Coding Development Languages C++, STL, Qt, QML Git. CI. CD Russian Dart, Flutter OOP, SOLID, TDD English **Boost** Algorithms, patterns German •000

Hobbies



Programming





Traveling



Reading



Btw, I use Arch

Strengths